Courtney Jackson Software Engineer | Business Owner

Los Angeles, CA | (323)619-4357 courtney_jackson1989@yahoo.com

Github: https://github.com/CourtneyAJackson Linked In: www.linkedin.com/in/courtney-abriana-jackson

WORK EXPERIENCE

General Assembly

Software Engineering Immersive | Engineering Fellow July 2021 - October 2021

- Completed 420 hours of immersive Software Development training
- Developed 4 fully functioning applications using Ruby on Rails, JavaScript, React, and Express framework.

Smokin' Greens LA - Food Business

Owner

March 2018 - present

- Managing and tracking day-to-day operations
- Planning and Strategy
- Staffing and Management
- Customer Service

Prive Revaux June 2018 – Jan 2020

Store Manager

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

General Assembly Immersive

Certificate of Completion | Software Engineering

West Los Angeles College

Business

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

With a strong passion for community service and outreach, my vegan food business has made healthier food options available to lower income communities for 3 plus years. As a business owner with 6 years of management experience, I bring a people-focused, proactive approach to my work as a software developer. I aim to become a part of a team that holds similar values and can make a difference with advancements in technology.

SKILLS & PROFICIENCIES

Software

- JavaScript
- · Ruby on Rails
- React
- HTML
- Css
- Express

Interpersonal Skills

- Interpersonal Skills
- Management
- Outreach programming

VOLUNTEER WORK

Aids Walk Annually

Habitat for Humanity New Orleans, LA 2005

Parent Elementary After School Program Inglewood CA 2002 - 2004